<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Isaac Bythewood</title><link href="http://isaacbythewood.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://isaacbythewood.com/feeds/gaming.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://isaacbythewood.com/</id><updated>2013-09-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated><entry><title>Payday 2</title><link href="http://isaacbythewood.com/2013/09/17/payday-2/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-09-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated><author><name>Isaac Bythewood</name></author><id>tag:isaacbythewood.com,2013-09-17:2013/09/17/payday-2/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;One of the funnest first person shooters I've ever played.*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* As long as you have 3 dedicated friends to play it with you. This game gets
very monotonous very fast if you don't have a group of friends to play with. The
AI is terrible and it's hard to finish most of the funner missions with them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That being said I did have 3 dedicated friends to play this game with and it was
great. We've already had hours of fun and will have more in the future. The
developers seem to update the game often and, while it still feels a bit buggy
and beta-ish, I feel like they are updating the game and fixing stuff at a
reasonable rate. I plan on continuing to play this game for many more months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I highly recommend checking it out, &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://store.steampowered.com/app/218620"&gt;it's on steam&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Links --&gt;
</summary></entry><entry><title>Super House of Dead Ninjas</title><link href="http://isaacbythewood.com/2013/05/08/super-house-of-dead-ninjas/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-05-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated><author><name>Isaac Bythewood</name></author><id>tag:isaacbythewood.com,2013-05-08:2013/05/08/super-house-of-dead-ninjas/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;An incredible fast paced platformer. You have to fight your way down to the
bottom of a tower killing monsters, collecting items, and getting upgrades. The
tower is randomly generated and you get new items everytime. I enjoyed playing
this game for quite a few hours and could easily get in the groove and zone out.
A perfect game after a long day's work for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I can't highly recommend this game I still think it's a fun time waster
and worth a few playthroughs, &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://store.steampowered.com/app/224820"&gt;it's on steam&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Links --&gt;
</summary></entry><entry><title>Super Meat Boy</title><link href="http://isaacbythewood.com/2013/05/08/super-meat-boy/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-05-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated><author><name>Isaac Bythewood</name></author><id>tag:isaacbythewood.com,2013-05-08:2013/05/08/super-meat-boy/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I should have played this game when it was released. It's incredible, I love how
fast everything is and collecting bandages to unlock all the characters. I also
can't go without mentioning the soundtrack. It was made by Danny B and fits the
game amazingly well. If you like a fast paced platformer this is for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My only complaint are that the leaderboards are full of people who cheated with
a time of 0.00, if you have friends who play this game you can look at your
friends leaderboard times but don't bother comparing yourself globally to the
cheaters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I highly recommend checking it out immediately, &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://store.steampowered.com/app/40800"&gt;it's on steam&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Links --&gt;
</summary></entry><entry><title>Sword of the Stars: The Pit</title><link href="http://isaacbythewood.com/2013/03/25/sword-of-the-stars-the-pit/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-03-25T00:00:00-04:00</updated><author><name>Isaac Bythewood</name></author><id>tag:isaacbythewood.com,2013-03-25:2013/03/25/sword-of-the-stars-the-pit/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A game that you need to stick with to actually enjoy. There is no tutorial and
it is very hard. You will die. I recommend gathering some recipes in easy mode
before progressing to harder difficulties. Since The Pit is perma-death you can
get to the 30th floor and die with the end at the edge of your monitor and you
will cry because it might take you 20 hours to get there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you do happen to beat it though it is a very rewarding experience simply
because of how hard it is. You feel very accomplished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I can't highly recommend this game I still think it's fun and worth
beating, &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://store.steampowered.com/app/233700"&gt;it's on steam&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Links --&gt;
</summary></entry><entry><title>Faster Than Light</title><link href="http://isaacbythewood.com/2012/12/21/faster-than-light/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-12-21T00:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Isaac Bythewood</name></author><id>tag:isaacbythewood.com,2012-12-21:2012/12/21/faster-than-light/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;As a huge SciFi and space exploration fanatic I am unsure why I haven't picked
this game up before. It's a great example of a simple, straightforward indie
game that encompasses days of fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The overall play is basic, you have a ship, you improve your ship with upgrades
and manage it's systems along with it's crew repair your ship while fighting off
other ships. Your goal is to get to your home words/base and defend it from the
&amp;quot;Rebels&amp;quot;. Along the way you have a bunch of mini-quests and save a bunch of
people of which all are optional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you beat the game you unlock more ships to start with which have different
abilities and different playstyles. Each playthrough is semi-randomized giving
you a unique experience every time. Overall this game goes down as one of the
best I've ever played, definitely the best indie-game I've ever played.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I highly recommend checking it out, &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://store.steampowered.com/app/212680"&gt;it's on steam&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Links --&gt;
</summary></entry><entry><title>PlanetSide 2</title><link href="http://isaacbythewood.com/2012/12/18/planetside-2/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-12-18T00:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Isaac Bythewood</name></author><id>tag:isaacbythewood.com,2012-12-18:2012/12/18/planetside-2/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;An insanely fun FPS that does the free to play model very well. I've personally
spent about 120 bucks on this game but have quite a few friends keeping up with
me who have spent absolutely nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basically think of the game as BF3 but on a massive scale. Some of the mechanics
aren't as clean as BF3 but the sheer size of the fights you find yourself in
makes it insanely enjoyable none-the-less.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I highly recommend checking it out immediately, &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://store.steampowered.com/app/218230"&gt;it's on steam&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Links --&gt;
</summary></entry><entry><title>Natural Selection 2</title><link href="http://isaacbythewood.com/2012/10/18/natural-selection-2/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-10-18T00:00:00-04:00</updated><author><name>Isaac Bythewood</name></author><id>tag:isaacbythewood.com,2012-10-18:2012/10/18/natural-selection-2/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you enjoy RTS or FPS this is a great game, if you enjoy both it's the
greatest game. I really enjoy playing an alien commander and building upgrades
and bases tossing out cysts everywhere, or playing the extremely team oriented
marines and helping clear out a hallway of skulks. Lots of fun no matter how you
play it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only warning I have is that there is a steep learning curve, don't play
commander for a while and do play the tutorial, you really need to learn how to
play it or your team will hate you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I highly recommend checking it out immediately, &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://store.steampowered.com/app/4920"&gt;it's on steam&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Links --&gt;
</summary></entry></feed>